An important part of being a software engineer is designing good data structures.
作为软件工程师一个重要的部分 是要设计好的数据结构
This question asks us, how do we modify our index
这个问题问的是 我们如何修改索引
so that we can track the number of times users click a link for a given keyword?
使得我们能够追踪 使用者对某个关键词点击链接的次数
This allows us to sort the results in our search engine based on how popular the links are.
这允许我们的搜索引擎 根据链接的受欢迎程度来进行排序
Let's go through the choices one by one
让我们一个一个地检查这些选项
and come up with some examples to see the effects those choices can have
举一些例子 看看在实作搜索引擎时
on an implemented search engine.
这些选项会有什么样的影响
Given this is an answer choice, it may be a little hard to reason about what it would look like
这做为答案的选项 要理解它会是什么样子可能有些困难
if you actually used it in your search engine,
如果你在搜索引擎中实际地使用它
so let's come up with an example.
现在 让我们举个例子
The keyword "andy" is associated with 2 URLs:
关键词 'andy' 与 2 个 url 相关
"udacity.com" and "searchwithpeter.info"
'udacity.com' 和 'searchwithpeter.info'
and the keyword "irvin" is associated with "udacity.com".
关键词 'irvin' 与 'udacity.com' 相关
And then I have the counts, 5 and 8.
然后我有这个计数 (count) 5 和 8
Ideally, for this to be useful we want to count the number of times a user clicks the URL
理想情况下 对于特定的关键词 我们要数 (count)
given a certain keyword.
使用者点击这个网址的次数
That way we can sort these 2 URLs based on the counts
我们可以根据计数 (count) 为了服务使用者得到更好的搜索结果
in order to serve our users better search results.
对这 2 个网址进行排序
At this stands now, there's only 1 count for each keyword.
而现在 对于每个关键词 计数只有 1 个
This might be useful to count the number of times people search things,
计数人们搜索事物的次数 可能很有用
but it doesn't help us solve our problem, so this is no good.
但它对于解决我们的问题没有帮助 所以这个选项并不好
Here I've numerated the second choice.
这是第二个选项
What's useful about this is that we have a count for each URL and each keyword.
这个选项有用的原因是 对于每个 url 与关键词 都有个计数
This allows us to sort these 2 URLs.
这允许我们对这 2 个 url 进行排序
We can add "searchwithpeter.info" above "udacity.com"
当我们在网页上显示结果
when we display our results on the web page
我们可以在 'udacity.com' 上面 加入 'searchwithpeter.info'
because users more often click that link than the other.
因为使用者通常点击这个链接更多于其他链接
This seems like a pretty good choice, and it turns out to be the best one
这似乎是个相当不错的选项 而事实证明它是最好的一个
so it gets a check.
所以我们将要选择它
This data structure doesn't really make that much sense.
这个数据结构并非真的有那么多的意义
Why do we have multiple counts corresponding to a single URL?
为什么对于单个 url 要有多个计数 (count) 呢?
You could imagine a use for it, maybe that each count
你可以想像使用它时
corresponds to a certain period of time,
也许每个计数对应于某一段时间
but given what we have here, it's probably not the best data structure
但根据我们所有的 它可能不是最佳的数据结构
for exactly what we want to do and that is just sort the queries results
而究竟我们要做什么呢？就只是对查询结果做排序
based strictly on the number of clicks.
根据严格的点击数
For this one I don't need to even go into an example.
对这个选项 我甚至不需要举例
This is the same as the first choice,
这和第一个选项相同
except keyword was moved over a position and count was also moved over.
除了关键词移动了位置 而且计数移动了位置
For the same reason as before, namely that we only have 1 count for the keyword
与之前的原因相同 也就是对于关键词只有 1 个计数
instead of for each URL, this isn't the right solution.
而不是对每个 url 所以这不是正确的解答